https://publiclibraries.com/privacy-policy/

Public Records
Obituaries
Last Revision Date: 3/30/2018
PublicLibraries.com respects everyone’s right to privacy and your privacy is important to us. We publish this Privacy Policy to inform you of our privacy practices applicable to our website located at publiclibraries.com (“Website”).
Personally Identifiable Information
PublicLibraries.com only collects information that personally identifies you (such as your name and email address) if you choose to share it with us. If you choose to contact us via our contact form you will be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information so that we may respond to you via email. If you choose not to provide this information, we will be unable to reply to any attempts to contact us.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
PublicLibraries.com automatically collects non-personally identifiable information when you use our Website. We collect the typical usage information that is provided by your web browser at the time of your visit. This information may include your IP address, browser type, operating system, pages viewed, referring URL, and other related information. We store this information in our server log files.
Cookies and Web Beacons
PublicLibraries.com does not use cookies or web beacons.
Information Usage and Sharing
We use personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information collected at our Website for internal uses only. We use this information primarily to improve the quality and experience of our Website and to respond to emails we receive from our contact form. We will not sell or share this information to third parties unless required to do so by law.
Our Advertising Partners
We use third-party ad servers or ad networks that use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on publiclibraries.com and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site. PublicLibraries.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
Public Records Search and People Search Service
The “Public Records Search” and “People Search” services on publiclibraries.com are powered by BeenVerified. By using either of these services you agree to be bound by BeenVerified’s Terms of Use and Privacy Policy and to use BeenVerified in accordance with the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FCRA). All information gathered by these services is on forms that are hosted on BeenVerified’s site. PublicLibraries.com does NOT have access to any of the information (such as billing information or search criteria) provided in the forms required by either of these services offered by BeenVerified.
If you wish to have your information removed from the services offered by BeenVerified, there is an opt out form available on the BeenVerified website.
Compliance with Law
PublicLibraries.com works with government officials and private parties to comply with the law. We reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information to law enforcement and government officials and private parties if we believe it is required in order to comply with legal requests or with the law.
Children’s Privacy
The PublicLibraries.com Website is intended for use by adults only. We do not intentionally collect information from children under the age of 13. If we are notified that we have accidentally collected information from a child that is under the age of 13 we will immediately remove such information from our records. We do not knowingly distribute any information collected from children under the age of 13.
Privacy Policy Changes
PublicLibraries.com may update this Privacy Policy from time to time and we recommend that you review it periodically. We will inform our users by posting the revised Privacy Policy on our Website with a revision date. Continued use of our Website constitutes your consent to the revised Privacy Policy.
Privacy Policy Acceptance
When you use the PublicLibraries.com Website, you are agreeing to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of the PublicLibraries.com Website.
Social
Follow @PubLibs
